<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raymond</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Raymond</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 18:14:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://example.org/app1/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 18:14:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/app1/test/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dosha</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/dosha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 17:40:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/dosha/</guid>
      <description>Dosha
I’ve always enjoyed taking personality tests. I like things that help me better understand myself, and this shouldn’t be a surprise because I have a blog dedicated to reflecting and musings.
I recently heard Dr.K talk about how it’s important to understand your Dosha. Or maybe he didn’t say that, but rather, that Doshas can be a good way to understand yourself. In his case, understanding that he was Vata meant going from a failing student to Harvard psychiatrist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Creative Lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/a-creative-lifestyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 21:39:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/a-creative-lifestyle/</guid>
      <description>On Creativity
I was walking to a salsa event with one of my friends. She told me how, as a photographer, I’m probably used to being isolated to work on projects. I was confused.
I’ve don’t consider myself a creative person. I like making jokes and writing semi-interesting stories, but it’s never felt creative. It wasn’t until I started reading Big Magic that I started wondering what creativity means to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning From Failure</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/learning-from-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 18:20:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/learning-from-failure/</guid>
      <description>In 2015, I wrote a series of essays for college applications, and this might be one of my favorites because it summarizes my thoughts on life.
I left my house and started running my usual route. I passed houses and continued to follow the white, concrete pavement until I arrived at the park. Jogging there was the warmup, and the actual workout would begin at the park. I started sprinting up and down a field until breathing became a struggle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 18:13:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/updates/</guid>
      <description>Where I’ve Been
It’s been 8 months since I’ve last publicly written something. And the time really flew by quickly, since November 2020, I’m not really sure what I’ve been doing. In January, I started becoming involved with political discussion, and I would listen to Destiny debate various topics. At the same time, I was intensely studying poker to improve my ability in the game. And overall, I think the year of poker was a decent success, although I’ll save that story for another day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding with Raymond - How to Get Minecraft on a Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/the-amazing-chromeos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 23:16:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/the-amazing-chromeos/</guid>
      <description>I have two sisters that are in 6th grade. Because their brains are so malleable, I figured I’d introduce them into the first step of using computers, by playing Minecraft. In most cases, it’d be simple. Just buy Minecraft and tell them to download it. Unfortunately, this did not happen.
They told me they were using ChromeOS, which can’t run Minecraft. Everything was downhill from there. This is the cautionary tale of my journey to ChromeOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m spending $1000 to learn Korean</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/learning-korean-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 22:11:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/learning-korean-1/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE: I failed at this challenge and it exists now only as click-bait. I went to about 4 classes before ultitamtely giving up and probably watching television instead. But I think this could be a cool idea for a future challenge
Since August of 2019, I’ve been learning Korean. For longest time, I’ve wanted to continue learning it, but I’ve been woefully unmotivated. That’s changing today, and I’m going to invest $1000 towards being able to speak the language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Invest</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/how-to-invest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 18:59:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/how-to-invest/</guid>
      <description>I’ve heard people describe investing as complicated or scary. I wanted to change that. I’ve read like 5 different finance books, and I like money. I end up telling my friends this stuff because I think it’s interesting. Also, investing late, or worse, never investing, can easily lose $100,000+ in gains.
Warren Buffet and most financial advisors agree that a lifecycle fund or an index fund is the best way to invest as a beginner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/my-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 19:03:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/my-story/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Books</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/best-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:49:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/best-books/</guid>
      <description>Programming Books
Cracking the Coding Interview
How much I&amp;rsquo;d Recommend it - 10/10
The book that introduced me to the world of interview problems. Has 150+ problems that will put you ahead of other candidates.
Elements of Programming Interviews Python
How much I&amp;rsquo;d Recommend it - 10/10
A book of even more problems than CTCI, AND they’re harder. I solved a lot of problems in this book, and I can easily say it helped on my interviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:48:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/now/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated: July 5th, 2021I’m currently living and working in Orlando. Being vaccinated means I can start shifting my old hobbies of being inside all day to having more social opportunities.
Working Full Time
I’ve been working as a developer at Citibank for a year. I’m also trying to solve every problem in the ELPI book. I think I’m at about 50 out of 200.
Getting Back into Weightlifting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College Decision Day</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/college-decision-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 14:34:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/college-decision-day/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that special, wonderful time of the year. Thousands of students wake up each month with a mixed sense of anxiety and excitement. When their classes end, they&amp;rsquo;ll go home and hear about how their friends got accepted into Duke and MIT, then they&amp;rsquo;ll schizophrenically debate with themselves whether they should check or not if they got into their dream school. I mean, if Thomas got in, then why shouldn&amp;rsquo;t they?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Post</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/new-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 14:34:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/new-post/</guid>
      <description>Some Example Text</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Post</title>
      <link>https://example.org/now/new-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 14:34:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/now/new-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quitting Videogames</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/quitting-videogames/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 18:33:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/quitting-videogames/</guid>
      <description>Another post from the articles. This is a chapter from my life, probably when I was 17 in 2015. It&amp;rsquo;s not super-polish and it might be one of my least favorite thigns I&amp;rsquo;ve writte. That said, I might as well leave it online for a little bit. I think I could edit it to have it be better.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing video games for a really long time. I spent a lot of time during my childhood with my grandma, because my mom worked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I want to Take a Gap Year</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/taking-a-gap-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 18:54:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/taking-a-gap-year/</guid>
      <description>When I tell my smart and studious IB friends that I want to take a break from college for a year, they look at me with a confused face. &amp;ldquo;Why on Earth would you do that!&amp;rdquo; it&amp;rsquo;s like I just took a crap on their lawn. And their reactions make sense; I&amp;rsquo;ve spent three years in a program designed to give me skills for college. Why would I not want to jump in?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>