<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Raymond</title>
    <link>https://example.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Raymond</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 23:16:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding with Raymond - How to Get Minecraft on a Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/the-amazing-chromeos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 23:16:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/the-amazing-chromeos/</guid>
      <description>I have two sisters that are in 6th grade. Because their brains are so malleable, I figured I’d introduce them into the first step of using computers, by playing Minecraft. In most cases, it’d be simple. Just buy Minecraft and tell them to download it. Unfortunately, this did not happen.
They told me they were using ChromeOS, which can’t run Minecraft. Everything was downhill from there. This is the cautionary tale of my journey to ChromeOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m spending $1000 to learn Korean</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/learning-korean-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 22:11:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/learning-korean-1/</guid>
      <description>Since August of 2019, I’ve been learning Korean. For longest time, I’ve wanted to continue learning it, but I’ve been woefully unmotivated. That’s changing today, and I’m going to invest $1000 towards being able to speak the language.
I’m doing this, partly because I want to be outrageous and partly because I want to commit to learning another language.
My Favorite Language Learning Strategies
I’m constantly evaluating my strategy, and I think I’ve found a winning one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Invest</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/how-to-invest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 18:59:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/how-to-invest/</guid>
      <description>I’ve heard people describe investing as complicated or scary. I wanted to change that. I’ve read like 5 different finance books, and I like money. I end up telling my friends this stuff because I think it’s interesting. Also, investing late, or worse, never investing, can easily lose $100,000+ in gains.
Warren Buffet and most financial advisors agree that a lifecycle fund or an index fund is the best way to invest as a beginner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/my-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 19:03:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/my-story/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Books</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/best-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:49:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/best-books/</guid>
      <description>Programming Books
Cracking the Coding Interview
How much I&amp;rsquo;d Recommend it - 10/10
The book that introduced me to the world of interview problems. Has 150+ problems that will put you ahead of other candidates.
Elements of Programming Interviews Python
How much I&amp;rsquo;d Recommend it - 10/10
A book of even more problems than CTCI, AND they’re harder. I solved a lot of problems in this book, and I can easily say it helped on my interviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:48:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/now/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated: November 17th, 2020Working Full Time
I’ve been developing software for Citibank since August. Most of my days are spent at my computer desk, which is a shocking difference to what I’m used to. Their office won’t be opening until March, so I might just live with my parents and save money until then.
Improving Cardio
I’ve been running probably the most since I was in high school, and I can thank David Goggins for motivating me for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College Decision Day</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/college-decision-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 14:34:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/college-decision-day/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that special, wonderful time of the year. Thousands of students wake up each month with a mixed sense of anxiety and excitement. When their classes end, they&amp;rsquo;ll go home and hear about how their friends got accepted into Duke and MIT, then they&amp;rsquo;ll schizophrenically debate with themselves whether they should check or not if they got into their dream school. I mean, if Thomas got in, then why shouldn&amp;rsquo;t they?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Post</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/new-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 14:34:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/new-post/</guid>
      <description>Some Example Text</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>